(Sheldon:)...with a slightly out-of-scale head
and a mild Dr Pepper addiction.
(Sheldon:)Anything you'd like to add?
That's not gonna get you anywhere.
Better pull out the big gun.
(Leonard:)You're right.
Let's talk about your grandmother.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)I call no meemaws.
(Raj:)Think about this.
(Raj:)The only way your mother was born
was your meemaw had sex.
[RAJESH & HOWARD CHUCKLING]
-I don't wanna hear this.
-Then let go of the ring and walk away.
(Leonard:)-Never.
-All right.
(Howard:)I'll bet your meemaw didn't just have sex
to have your mother...
(Howard:)...I bet she had sex...
[IN SULTRY VOICE]
...because she liked it.
[RAJESH & HOWARD CHUCKLING]
(Sheldon:)-Stop it.
-Yeah. Meemaw did the nasty.
(Sheldon:)-I said stop it!
RAJESH & HOWARD: Ha-ha-ha.
-[IN NORMAL VOICE] We're getting to him.
-Waterfalls.
(Leonard:)-What?
(Sheldon:)Crashing waves, babbling brooks.